<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<root>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>1</id>  
    <name>广东</name>  
    <docvec>广东 50 粤 50 广州 50 深圳 50 珠海 50 汕头 50 韶关 50 佛山 50 江门 50 湛江 50 茂名 50 肇庆 50 惠州 50 梅山 50 汕尾 50 河源 50 阳江 50 清远 50 潮州 50 揭阳 50 云浮 50 东莞 50 中山 50</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>2</id>  
    <name>浙江</name>  
    <docvec>浙江 50 杭州 50 西湖 50 宁波 50 温州 50 金华 50 台州 50 宁波 50 杭州 50 杭州市 50 宁波 50 宁波市 50 温州 50 温州市 50 嘉兴 50 嘉兴市 50 湖州 50 湖州市 50 绍兴 50 绍兴市 50 金华 50 金华市 50 台州 50 台州市 50 丽水 50 丽水市 50 舟山 50 舟山市 50 衢州 50 衢州市 50 永嘉 50 永嘉县 50 苍南 50 苍南县 50 文成 50 文成县 50 泰顺 50 泰顺县 50 临安 50 临安市 50 桐庐 50 桐庐县 50 建德 50 建德市 50 富阳 50 富阳市 50 奉化 50 奉化县 50 象山 50 象山县 50 海盐 50 海盐县 50 嘉善 50 嘉善县 50 上虞 50 上虞市 50 嵊州 50 嵊州市 50 绍兴 50 绍兴县 50 新昌 50 新昌县 50 武义 50 武义县 50 浦江 50 浦江县 50</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>3</id>  
    <name>江苏</name>  
    <docvec>南京 50 南京市 50 江宁区 50 栖霞区 50 浦口区 50 鼓楼区 50 建邺区 50 白下区 50 六合区 50 玄武区 50 下关区 50 秦淮区 50 高淳县 50 雨花区 50 溧水县 50 浦口区 50 无锡 50 无锡市 50 崇安 50 北塘 50 南长 50 滨湖 50 锡山 50 惠山 50 徐州 50 徐州市 50 云龙 50 鼓楼 50 铜山 50 贾汪 50 泉山 50 常州 50 常州市 50 钟楼 50 天宁 50 戚墅堰 50 新北 50 武进 50 苏州 50 苏州市 50 金阊 50 沧浪 50 平江 50 虎丘 50 吴中 50 相城 50 南通 50 南通市 50 崇川 50 港闸 50 通州 50 连云港 50 连云港市 50 新浦 50 连云 50 海州 50 淮安 50 淮安市 50 清河 50 清浦 50 楚州 50 淮阴 50 盐城 50 盐城市 50 亭湖 50 盐都 50 扬州 50 扬州市 50 维扬 50 广陵 50 邗江 50 镇江 50 镇江市 50 京口 50 润州 50 丹徒 50 泰州 50 泰州市 50 海陵 50 高港 50 宿迁 50 宿迁市 50 沭阳 50 泗阳 50 泗洪 50</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>4</id>  
    <name>安徽</name>  
    <docvec>安徽 20 合肥 20 皖 20 芜湖 20 蚌埠 20 淮南 20 马鞍山 20 淮北 20 铜陵 20 安庆 20 黄山 20 滁州 20 阜阳 20 宿州 20 六安 20 亳州 20 池州 20 宣城</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>5</id>  
    <name>山东</name>  
    <docvec>山东 20 济南 20 青岛 20 淄博 20 枣庄 20 东营 20 烟台 20 潍坊 20 威海 20 济宁 20 泰安 20 日照 20 莱芜 20 临沂 20 德州 20 聊城 20 滨州 20 菏泽 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>6</id>  
    <name>江西</name>  
    <docvec>江西 20 南昌 20 赣 20 景德镇 20 萍乡 20 九江 20 新余 20 鹰潭 20 赣州 20 吉安 20 宜春 20 抚州 20 上饶 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>7</id>  
    <name>福建</name>  
    <docvec>福建 20 福州 20 厦门 20 莆田 20 宁德 20 泉州 20 漳州 20 龙岩 20 三明 20 南平 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>8</id>  
    <name>海南</name>  
    <docvec>海南 20 海口 20 龙华 20 秀英区 20 琼山区 20 美兰区 20 三亚 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>9</id>  
    <name>上海</name>  
    <docvec>黄浦区 20 卢湾区 20 徐汇区 20 静安区 20 普陀区 20 闸北区 20 虹口区 20 杨浦区 20 闵行区 20 宝山区 20 嘉定区 20 浦东新区 20 金山区 20 松江区 20 青浦区 20 南汇区 20 奉贤区 20 崇明县 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>10</id>  
    <name>广西</name>  
    <docvec>广西 20 桂林 20 南宁 20 柳州 20 梧州 20 钦州 20 北海 20 玉林 20 贵港 20 防城港 20 百色 20 崇左 20 来宾 20 贺州 20 河池 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>11</id>  
    <name>河南</name>  
    <docvec>河南 20 郑州 20 开封 20 洛阳 20 平顶山 20 焦作 20 鹤壁 20 新乡 20 安阳 20 濮阳 20 许昌 20 漯河 20 三门峡 20 南阳 20 商丘 20 信阳 20 周口 20 驻马店 20 济源 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>12</id>  
    <name>河北</name>  
    <docvec>河北 20 石家庄 20 唐山 20 秦皇岛 20 邯郸 20 邢台 20 保定 20 张家口 20 承德 20 沧州 20 廊坊 20 衡水 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>13</id>  
    <name>山西</name>  
    <docvec>山西 20 晋 20 大同 20 太原 20 阳泉 20 长治 20 晋城 20 朔州 20 晋中 20 运城 20 忻州 20 临汾 20 吕梁 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>14</id>  
    <name>北京</name>  
    <docvec>北京 20 东城区 20 故宫 20 西城区 20 西单 20 王府井 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>15</id>  
    <name>内蒙古</name>  
    <docvec>内蒙古 20 呼尔浩特 20 包头 20 乌海 20 赤峰 20 通辽 20 鄂尔多斯 20 呼伦贝尔 20 巴彦淖尔 20 乌兰察布 20 兴安盟 20 锡林郭勒盟 20 阿拉善盟 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>16</id>  
    <name>辽宁</name>  
    <docvec>辽宁 20 沈阳 20 大连 20 鞍山 20 抚顺 20 本溪 20 丹东 20 锦州 20 营口 20 阜新 20 辽阳 20 盘锦 20 铁岭 20 朝阳 20 葫芦岛 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>17</id>  
    <name>吉林</name>  
    <docvec>吉林 20 长春 20 吉林 20 四平 20 辽源 20 通化 20 白山 20 松原 20 白城 20 延边朝鲜族自治州</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>18</id>  
    <name>黑龙江</name>  
    <docvec>黑龙江 20 哈尔滨 20 齐齐哈尔 20 鸡西 20 鹤岗 20 双鸭山 20 大庆 20 伊春 20 佳木斯 20 七台河 20 牡丹江 20 黑河 20 绥化 20 大兴安岭 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>19</id>  
    <name>湖南</name>  
    <docvec>湖南 20 长沙 20 株洲 20 湘潭 20 衡阳 20 邵阳 20 岳阳 20 常德 20 张家界 20 益阳 20 郴州 20 永州 20 怀化 20 娄底 20 湘西 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>20</id>  
    <name>湖北</name>  
    <docvec>湖北 20 武汉 20 鄂 20 黄石 20 襄樊 20 十堰 20 荆州 20 宜昌 20 荆门 20 鄂州 20 孝感 20 黄冈 20 咸宁 20 随州 20 恩施 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>21</id>  
    <name>贵州</name>  
    <docvec>贵州 20 贵阳 20 遵义 20 安顺 20 铜仁地区 20 毕节地区 20 黔西南州 20 黔东南州 20 黔南州 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>22</id>  
    <name>云南</name>  
    <docvec>云南 20 昆明 20 云贵 20 曲靖 20 玉溪 20 保山 20 邵通 20 丽江 20 普洱 20 临沧 20 文山 20 红河 20 西双版纳 20 楚雄 20 大理 20 德宏 20 怒江 20 迪庆 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>23</id>  
    <name>深圳</name>  
    <docvec>深圳 20 福田区 20 罗湖区 20 南山区 20 宝安区 20 龙岗区 20 盐田区</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>24</id>  
    <name>四川</name>  
    <docvec>四川 20 川 20 成都 20 自贡 20 攀枝花 20 泸州 20 德阳 20 绵阳 20 广元 20 遂宁 20 内江 20 乐山 20 南充 20 宜宾 20 广安 20 达州 20 眉山 20 雅安 20 巴中 20 资阳 20 阿坝州 20 甘孜州 20 凉山州 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>25</id>  
    <name>重庆</name>  
    <docvec>重庆 20 万洲 20 达县 20 渝中区 20 江北区 20 渝北区 20 巴南区 20 涪陵区 20 黔江区 20 长寿区 20 江津区 20 合川区 20 永川区 20 南川区</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>26</id>  
    <name>西藏</name>  
    <docvec>西藏 20 拉萨 20 昌都地区 20 山南地区 20 日喀则地区 20 那曲地区 20 阿里地区 20 林芝地区 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>27</id>  
    <name>青海</name>  
    <docvec>青海 20 西宁 20 海东地区 20 海北州 20 黄南州 20 海南州 20 果洛州 20 玉树州 10 海西州 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>28</id>  
    <name>陕西</name>  
    <docvec>陕西 20 西安 20 铜川 20 宝鸡 20 咸阳 20 渭南 20 延安 20 汉中 20 榆林 20 安康 20 商洛 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>29</id>  
    <name>甘肃</name>  
    <docvec>兰州 20 甘肃 20 金昌 20 白银 20 天水 20 武威 20 张掖 20 平凉 20 酒泉 20 庆阳 20 定西 20 陇南 20 临夏州 20 甘南州 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>30</id>  
    <name>海外</name>  
    <docvec>澳门 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>50</id>  
    <name>全国</name>  
    <docvec>全国 20</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>51</id>  
    <name>天津</name>  
    <docvec>天津市 50 和平区 50 河西区 50 南开区 50 河东区 50 河北区 50 红桥区 50 东丽区 50 津南区 50 西青区 50 北辰区 50 滨海新区 50 武清区 50 宝坻区 50 蓟县 50 宁河县 50 静海县 50</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>52</id>  
    <name>外国</name>  
    <docvec>阿尔巴尼亚 40 阿尔及利亚 40 阿尔马尼亚共和国 40 阿富汗 40 阿根廷 40 阿闻酋 40 拉伯联合酋长国 40 阿鲁巴 40 阿曼 40 阿塞拜疆 40 埃及 40 埃塞俄比亚 40 爱尔兰 40 爱沙尼亚 40 安道尔 40 安哥拉 40 安圭拉 40 安提瓜和巴布达 40 奥地利 40 澳大利亚 40 澳门 40 巴巴多斯 40 巴布亚新几内亚 40 巴哈马 40 巴基斯坦 40 巴拉圭 40 巴勒斯坦 40 巴林 40 巴拿马 40 巴西 40 白俄罗斯 40 百慕大 40 保加利亚 40 北马里亚纳 40 贝劳 40 贝宁 40 比利时 40 冰岛 40 波多黎各 40 波兰 40 玻利维亚 40 波斯尼亚和黑塞哥维那 40 博茨瓦纳 40 伯利兹 40 不丹 40 布基纳法索 40 布隆迪 40 布维岛 40 朝鲜 40 赤道几内亚 40 丹麦 40 德国 40 德意志联邦共和国 40 东帝汶 40 多哥 40 多米尼加共和国 40 多米尼克 40 俄罗斯 40 厄瓜多尔 40 厄立特里亚 40 法国 40 法兰西共和国 40 法罗群岛 40 法属波利尼西亚 40 法属圭亚那 40 法属南部领土 40 梵蒂冈 40 菲律宾 40 斐济 40 芬兰 40 佛得角 40 冈比亚 40 刚果 40 哥伦比亚 40 哥斯达黎加 40 格林纳达 40 格陵兰 40 格鲁吉亚 40 古巴 40 瓜德罗普 40 关岛 40 圭亚那 40 哈萨克斯坦 40 海地 40 韩国 40 大韩民国 40 荷兰 40 荷属安的列斯 40 赫德岛和麦克唐纳岛 40 洪都拉斯 40 基里巴斯 40 吉布提 40 吉尔吉斯斯坦 40 几内亚 40 加拿大 40 几内亚比绍 40 加纳 40 加蓬 40 柬埔寨 40 捷克 40 津巴布韦 40 喀麦隆 40 卡塔尔 40 开曼群岛 40 科科斯群岛 40 基林群岛 40 科摩罗 40 科特迪瓦 40 科威特 40 克罗地亚 40 肯尼亚 40 库克群岛 40 拉脱维亚 40 莱索托 40 老挝 40 黎巴嫩 40 利比里亚 40 利比亚 40 立陶宛 40 列支敦士登 40 留尼汪 40 卢森堡 40 卢旺达 40 罗马尼亚 40 马达加斯加 40 马耳他 40 马尔代夫 40 马尔维纳斯群岛 40 福克兰群岛 40 马拉维 40 马来西亚 40 马里 40 马斯顿 40 马绍尔群岛 40 马提尼克 40 马约特 40 毛里求斯 40 毛里塔尼亚 40 美国 40 利坚合众国 40 美属萨摩亚 40 美属太平洋各群岛 40 美属太平洋中途岛 40 美属太平洋约翰斯顿岛 40 美属太平洋豪兰岛 40 美属太平洋贝克岛 40 美属太平洋威克岛 40 美属维尔京群岛 40 蒙古 40 蒙特塞拉特 40 孟加拉国 40 秘鲁 40 密克罗尼西亚 40 缅甸 40 摩尔多瓦 40 摩洛哥 40 摩洛哥 40 莫桑比克 40 墨西哥 40 纳米比亚 40 南非 40 南极洲 40 南乔治亚岛和南桑德韦奇岛 40 南斯拉夫 40 瑙鲁 40 尼泊尔 40 尼加拉瓜 40 尼日尔 40 尼日利亚 40 纽埃 40 挪威 40 诺福克岛 40 皮特凯恩群岛 40 皮竺凯恩群岛 40 葡萄牙 40 日本 40 瑞典 40 瑞士 40 萨尔瓦多 40 塞拉利昂 40 塞内加尔 40 塞浦路斯 40 沙竺阿拉伯 40 沙特阿拉伯王国 40 塞舌尔 40 圣诞岛 40 圣多美和普林西比 40 圣赫勒拿 40 圣基茨和尼维斯 40 圣革茨和尼维斯联邦 40 圣卢西亚 40 圣马力诺 40 圣皮埃尔和密克隆 40 圣文森特和格林纳丁斯 40 斯里兰卡 40 斯洛伐克 40 斯洛文尼亚 40 斯瓦尔巴群岛 40 斯威士兰 40 苏丹 40 苏里南 40 索马里 40 所罗门群岛 40 年罗门群岛 40 塔吉克斯坦 40 泰国 40 泰王国 40 坦桑尼亚 40 汤加 40 特克斯科斯群岛 40 特克斯和凯科斯群岛 40 特立尼达和多巴哥 40 突尼斯 40 图瓦卢 40 土耳其 40 土库曼斯坦 40 托克劳 40 瓦利斯和富图纳群岛 40 瓦努阿图 40 危地马拉 40 委内瑞拉 40 文莱 40 乌干达 40 乌克兰 40 乌拉圭 40 乌兹别克斯坦 40 西班牙 40 西撒哈拉 40 西萨摩亚 40 希腊 40 香港 40 新加坡 40 新喀里多尼亚 40 新西兰 40 匈牙利 40 叙利亚 40 牙买加 40 亚美尼亚 40 也门 40 伊拉克 40 伊朗 40 以色列 40 意大利 40 印度 40 印度尼西亚 40 英国 40 大不列颠及北爱尔兰联合王国 40 英属维尔京群岛 40 英属印度洋领土 40 约旦 40 越南 40 赞比亚 40 扎伊尔 40 乍得 40 直布罗陀 40 智利 40 中非 40</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>53</id>  
    <name>宁夏</name>  
    <docvec>宁夏 40 银川市 40 银川 40 石嘴山市 40 石嘴山 40 吴忠市 40 吴忠 40 固原市 40 固原 40 中卫市 40</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
  <com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province> 
    <id>54</id>  
    <name>新疆</name>  
    <docvec>新疆 40 乌鲁木齐市 40 乌鲁木齐 40 克拉玛依市 40 克拉玛依 40 吐鲁番地区 40 吐鲁番 40 哈密地区 40 哈密 40 昌吉回族自治州 40 博尔塔拉蒙古自治州 40 巴音郭楞蒙古自治州 40 阿克苏地区 40 阿克苏 40 克孜勒苏柯尔克孜自治州 40 喀什地区 40 喀什 40 和田地区 40 和田 40 伊犁哈萨克自治州 40 塔城地区 40 塔城 40 阿勒泰地区 40 阿勒泰 40 石河子市 40 石河子 40 阿拉尔市 40 阿拉尔 40 图木舒克市 40 图木舒克 40 五家渠市 40 五家渠 40</docvec> 
  </com.analyze.model.bean.persist.Province>
</root>
